http://www.nexsens.com/support/privacy-policy

Privacy PolicyNexSens Technology’s Customer Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected as you interact with our company, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase products and services, or when you call our sales or support associates. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information safeguard practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used, for what purposes and to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at NexSens, and we go to great lengths to protect it.Why We Collect Personal InformationWe collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.If you do not want NexSens to keep you up to date with news, software updates and the latest information on products and services, notify us in writing via the email or postal address shown below so that we can update your personal contact information and preferences.What Information We Collect & How We May Use ItThere are a few situations in which your personal information may help us serve you better. For example, we may ask for your personal information when you’re discussing a service issue on the phone with an associate, downloading a software update, or purchasing a product. We may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences; your credit card information and information about the NexSens products you own, such as their serial numbers and dates of purchase; and information relating to a support or service issue.NexSens takes your privacy very seriously. We do not sell or rent your contact information to other parties. Additionally, NexSens does not store your personal credit card information.Cookies and Other TechnologiesNexSens Technology’s websites and online services may use cookies and other technologies. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, indicate which parts of our websites people have visited, and facilitate the optimization of the website efficiency. To the extent that personal information is contained in cookies and other technologies, we treat the information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.If you want to prevent the use of cookies, check with your internet browser provider to find out how to disable cookies. Certain features of the NexSens website may not function properly once cookies are disabled.With Our Service Providers, Vendors & Strategic PartnersThere are also times when it may be advantageous for NexSens to make certain personal information about you available to companies with which NexSens has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for NexSens to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with NexSens’ policies.At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose personal information. We may also disclose information if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.Changes To This Privacy PolicyNexSens may update this privacy policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated privacy policy.Our Company-Wide Commitment To Your PrivacyNexSens takes protecting your privacy very seriously. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to NexSens employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company. In addition, NexSens supports industry initiatives to preserve privacy rights on the Internet and in all aspects of electronic commerce.Questions & SuggestionsIf you have questions, concerns or suggestions, please email us at info@nexsens.com or you can contact us at: NexSens Technology, Inc. Customer Care – Privacy Policy Issues 2091 Exchange Ct Fairborn, OH 45324 Phone: 937-426-2703 Fax: 937-426-1125
